[
    {
        "number": 0,
        "question": "What should we provide community education on?",
        "choice0": "The origin and nature of the pandemic",
        "choice1": "How to enjoy Chinese food without getting covid",
        "choice2": "How to achieve herd immunity",
        "choice3": "Where to get free rapid tests",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "What do the recommendations suggest we help the community with?",
        "choice0": "Their increasingly expensive grocery bills",
        "choice1": "Information overload from social media during covid",
        "choice2": "Their fears and stigmas about Asians during Covid-19",
        "choice3": "None of the above",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "What should be challenged?",
        "choice0": "False information about the pandemic only",
        "choice1": "Oppressive information about the pandemic only",
        "choice2": "False and oppressive information coming from public and authority figures ",
        "choice3": "A and B only",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "We should help the community at large understand that each person's health and related fears are the responsibility of this individual or group:",
        "choice0": "People's followers on social media",
        "choice1": "The person themselves",
        "choice2": "The Asian community",
        "choice3": "All of the above",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "What's true about anti-Asian racism?",
        "choice0": "Anti-Asian racism has been exacerbated by covid",
        "choice1": "Anti-Asian racism only started with covid",
        "choice2": "Anti-Asian racism can be solved by following 16 specific recommendations",
        "choice3": "A and C",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "We should counterbalance the overwhelming amount of information on the negative side of covid with which of the following information?",
        "choice0": "Positive and proactive information",
        "choice1": "What individuals can do to protect their safety",
        "choice2": "What individuals can do to support their loved ones who have contracted covid",
        "choice3": "All of the above",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "number": 6,
        "question": "When can we provide support to individuals experiencing anti-Asian racism?",
        "choice0": "On site during the incident",
        "choice1": "After the incident",
        "choice2": "Never",
        "choice3": "A and B",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "number": 7,
        "question": "The immediate and long term impacts of racism for its survivors include which one of these elements?",
        "choice0": "Practical and mental ",
        "choice1": "Psychological, interpersonal and spiritual",
        "choice2": "None of the above",
        "choice3": "A and B",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "number": 8,
        "question": "How should perpetrators of racist hate crimes be treated?",
        "choice0": "Receive unconditional forgiveness ",
        "choice1": "Be tarred and feathered",
        "choice2": "Bear legal responsibility for their behaviour",
        "choice3": "A and C",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "What may be helpful for individuals who choose to use faith practices for coping with racism and covid 19 related issues?",
        "choice0": "Make it illegal ",
        "choice1": "Respect individual choices",
        "choice2": "Make everyone engage in a faith practice",
        "choice3": "Tolerate it as long as they aren't engaging in the wrong faith practices",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "What may be helpful for clients experiencing racist treatment?",
        "choice0": "Empower them with strategies to deal with racist treatment and information on community resources",
        "choice1": "Empower them with enrollment at a local martial arts gym",
        "choice2": "Empower them with assurances that it's not as bad as they think it is",
        "choice3": "Tell them that there is no such thing as racism because ignorance is bliss",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "number": 11,
        "question": "What is one of the major groups who are especially at risk of experiencing racism and may need regular check-ins so we can provide support as the need arises?",
        "choice0": "Anyone with a large social networks",
        "choice1": "People with limited English or French for accessing community support",
        "choice2": "Essential service workers",
        "choice3": "Gen-Z",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "number": 12,
        "question": "What may be helpful for essential service workers and other service providers in their work helping survivors of anti-Asian racism?",
        "choice0": "Recognize and support them in their work so they feel valued and can be maximally effective",
        "choice1": "Ensure mainly Asians to work directly with survivors since they are more likely to understand their clients' struggles",
        "choice2": "Ensure fewer Asians need to work directly with survivors to prevent triggering traumas",
        "choice3": "Nothing. It's their job. ",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "number": 13,
        "question": "Who should work together to serve survivors of anti-Asian racism?",
        "choice0": "Mainly Asians",
        "choice1": "Mainly Asians and non-Asian racialized communities",
        "choice2": "Mainly Asians, non-Asian racialized communities, and racial allies",
        "choice3": "Mainly Asians, non-Asian racialized communities, racial allies, and the Secretary of Homeland Security",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "number": 14,
        "question": "Which is the false statement?",
        "choice0": "Politicians are responsible for addressing racism",
        "choice1": "We're almost done with this quiz",
        "choice2": "We should engage in dialogue with politicians about their responsibilities with regards to racism   ",
        "choice3": "Politicians are responsible for solving racism",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "number": 15,
        "question": "What shouldn't we do?",
        "choice0": "Instill hope about the pandemic coming to an end",
        "choice1": "Instill hope about racism coming to an end",
        "choice2": "Help people accept the historical and indefinite nature of the pandemic and racism",
        "choice3": "Help each other accept that today's session is almost done and we'll all have to go home soon",
        "answer": 2
    }
]